Some people in the US have asserted that forgiving student loan debt is one way to stimulate the economy and give assistance to those in need.
美国有人断言，免除学生贷款债务是刺激经济、帮助有需要者的办法之一。
One government proposition is to eliminate $10,000 of debt for ‘economically distressed’ students.
政府的一项提议是，为“经济困窘”的学生免除10,000美元的债务。
Some in the US Congress have gone so far as to suggest forgiving up to $50,000 in debt per student borrower, but does forgiving student debt necessarily correlate to helping the economically disadvantaged?
美国国会的一些议员甚至提议，为每名学生借款人免除最多50,000美元的债务，但免除学生债务就一定意味着帮到了经济上处于弱势的人吗？
The answer is no.
答案是否定的。
This policy is just giving money away to universities and the most affluent students in attendance.
这项政策只不过是在把钱白白送给大学和最富裕的在读学生。
Federal Reserve data reveals that the highest-income 40 percent of households owe approximately 60 percent of outstanding student debt, while the lowest 40 percent owe just under 20 percent.
美联储的数据显示，收入最高的40%家庭欠着约60%的未偿学生债务，而收入最低的40%家庭所欠的略低于20%。
This could be due to a combination of factors: students from high-income households are more likely to go to expensive colleges, less likely to receive financial aid, and more likely to have high incomes post-graduation.
这可能是多种因素共同造成的：来自高收入家庭的学生，上收费昂贵大学的可能性更大，获得经济资助的可能性更小，毕业后拿高收入的可能性也更大。
Plus, the majority of student debt is held by graduate degree earners, who earn approximately 25 percent more than their undergraduate counterparts.
此外，大部分学生债务背在获得研究生学位的人身上，而这些人的收入比获得本科学位的人高出约25%。
Clearly, giving free rein to banks to forgive student debt is a step in the wrong direction.
显然，放手让银行免除学生债务，是朝错误方向迈出的一步。
Other proposals for broader, long-term student loan plans have some fundamental problems.
其他一些提议主张推行范围更广的长期学生贷款计划，这些提议存在一些根本性问题。
One idea is to cancel student debt only for undergraduate degrees and for students making less than $125,000.
有一种设想是，只免除攻读本科学位所欠的学生债务，而且只针对收入低于125,000美元的学生。
This attempts to address the fact that Congress’ previously mentioned student loan forgiveness plan largely helps out the wealthy, but is an adverse incentive for universities to keep raising tuition and for students to choose to major in low-earning degree programs.
这一设想试图解决这样一个问题：前文提到的国会学生贷款免除计划主要帮助的是富人；但这一设想却是一种不良激励，会促使大学不断提高学费，也会促使学生选择主修毕业后收入低的专业。
Colleges have no reason to make their programs more affordable if they believe students will just take out more debt.
如果大学认为学生只会去借更多的债，它们就没有理由让自己开设的专业收费更实惠。
And students will feel more comfortable making the irresponsible decision to go tens of thousands of dollars in debt to major in impractical or idealistic subjects if they know their loans will be forgiven.
而且，学生如果知道自己的贷款会得到免除，就会更心安理得地做出不负责任的决定，背上数万美元的债务，去主修不切实际或理想化的学科。
This is especially concerning given the pandemic has rendered a college education practically worthless.
考虑到这场大流行病已使大学教育几乎变得毫无价值，这一点尤其令人担忧。
Students are paying tens of thousands of dollars per year to live at home and be lectured on the Internet.
学生们每年要花数万美元，就为了住在家里、在网上听课。
Do we really want to tell colleges that they can get away with providing below-average service for an outrageous cost?
我们真的想告诉大学，它们可以收取高得离谱的费用，提供低于平均水平的服务，却不必承担后果吗？
In the case of any of these student debt plans, working-class Americans who chose not to or could not afford to go to college will be subsidizing the education of the professional class.
无论实施这些学生债务计划中的哪一项，美国工人阶级中那些选择不上大学或上不起大学的人，都将补贴专业人士阶层的教育。
Plumbers and retail workers will be paying for the degrees of doctors and lawyers.
水管工和零售业员工将为医生和律师的学位买单。
The US government’s effort to help those in debt is commendable, but is this really the solution that will help the poor financially recover?
美国政府帮助负债者的努力值得称赞，但这真的是能帮助穷人在经济上恢复元气的解决办法吗？